http://meditationinleeds.org/about-us/privacy-policy/

Skip to Main Content
Privacy Policy
Privacy Notice
Effective date – 25 May 2018
Ratnasambhava Kadampa Buddhist Centre takes your privacy seriously, and any personal information that we collect from you will only be used for management and administration purposes. However this information is collected we will keep it secure and will not pass it on unless we have your permission. You may tell us at any time if you no longer wish us to retain your information, or if you wish us to correct it and unless we have a lawful reason for retaining it we will correct, destroy or delete it.
This privacy notice tells you what to expect when Ratnasambhava Kadampa Buddhist Centre collects information.
How we use your information
Visitors to our websites
Use of cookies
See below for more details.
E-newsletter
Ratnasambhava Kadampa Buddhist Centre uses a third party provider, Vertical Response, to deliver our e-newsletters. For more information, please see vertical response’s privacy policy at www.deluxe.com/policy/privacy-shield. Newsletters are only sent to people who have agreed to sign-up for the newsletter and have supplied their email address.
People who use our online booking system
Information collected and processed is necessary to manage and administer your booking, and to facilitate event planning. We may contact you via email or phone regarding your booking. We use PayPal as a payment system for events. For more information please see PayPal’s privacy policies.
People who email us
We monitor any emails sent to us, including file attachments, for viruses or malicious software. Please be aware that you have a responsibility to ensure that any email you send is within the bounds of the law.
How long we keep your information
Your information will be retained for as long as is necessary, within legal limits and obligations.
Your information used for marketing purposes will be kept until you notify us that you no longer wish to receive this information.
Links to other websites
This privacy notice does not cover the links within this site linking to other websites. We encourage you to read the privacy statements on the other websites you visit.
Changes to this privacy notice
We keep our privacy notice under regular review. This privacy notice was last updated on 25 May 2018.
Access to and amending your personal information
You may ask us to correct or remove information that we hold on you. Please contact us using the details below.
What you can do
If you are not satisfied with how we have dealt with your query, you may raise a complaint with the Information Commissioner’s Office ico.org.uk
How to contact us
If you want to request information about our privacy policy please use our contact form (located on our website) or write to:
Ratnasambhava Kadampa Buddhist Centre
22 Wetherby Road
Oakwood
Leeds LS8 2QD
Use of cookies by Ratnasambhava Kadampa Buddhist Centre
Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer by websites that you visit. They are widely used in order to make websites work, or work more efficiently, as well as to provide information to the owners of the site. The table below explains the cookies we use and why.
Third parties, including Facebook, may use cookies, web beacons, and other storage technologies to collect or receive information from this website and elsewhere on the internet and use that information to provide measurement services and target ads.
You can opt out of collection of information and third party adverts by going to the following websites and following the instructions provided by them –
www.aboutads.info/choices
www.youronlinechoices.eu/
Cookie
Name
Purpose
ShareThis: Free Social Share Buttons & Plugins for Websites & Blogs
contently_insights_user
__unam
__sharethis_cookie_test__
__stid
st_optout
ShareThis (http://www.sharethis.com) is used to allow the website users to share articles and pages on the website via social media.
Universal Analytics (Google)
_ga
_gid
__utma
gadwp_wg_default_dimension
gadwp_wg_default_metric
gadwp_wg_default_swmetric
These cookies are used to collect information about how visitors use the website. We use the information to compile reports and to help us improve the website. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of visitors to the website and blog, where visitors have come to the website from and the pages they visited.
Read Google’s overview of privacy and safeguarding data
WordPress
Wp-settings-1
wp-settings-time-1
wordpress_test_cookie
To help run WordPress, the Web publishing application for the website.
For more details go to –
https://wordpress.com/
https://codex.wordpress.org/WordPress_Cookies
Mailmunch
mailmunch_second_pageview
Used to manage subscription service to mailing lists. For more details see https://www.mailmunch.co/
Facebook
Facebook Pixel
Facebook may use cookies, web beacons, and other storage technologies to collect or receive information from this website and elsewhere on the internet and use that information to provide measurement services and target ads.
You can opt out of collection of information and third party adverts by going to the following websites and following the instructions provided by them –
www.aboutads.info/choices
www.youronlinechoices.eu/
For more details go to www.facebook.com/business/learn/facebook-ads-pixel
PHPSESSID
Cookie generated by applications based on the PHP language. This is a general purpose identifier used to maintain user session variables.
Visual Website Optimiser (VWO)
_vwo_uuid_v2
This cookie collects information about how visitors interact with the pages on the website. The information is used to compile reports and to help improve the site. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form. The information obtained does not identify anyone.
For more details go to
https://vwo.com/privacy-policy/
Jetpack
jetpackState[message]
Stores the state message passed back to the user across requests
regarding module activation.For more details see https://jetpack.com/
How do I change my cookie settings?
Most web browsers allow some control of most cookies through the browser settings. To find out more about cookies, including how to see what cookies have been set, visit www.aboutcookies.org
or www.allaboutcookies.org.
Find out how to manage cookies on popular browsers:
To find information relating to other browsers, visit the browser developer’s website.
To opt out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites, visit http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.
*
Contact Us
Name (required)
Email (required)
© 2020 Ratnasambhava Kadampa Buddhist Centre - Registered charity 1129195.
A member of the New Kadampa Tradition - International Kadampa Buddhist Union. All rights reserved.
